Once upon a time, there was a man who died.
The man's work was the writing and telling of stories,
but he could not defy death.
The last story he was working on was about a brave and handsome prince
who vanquishes a crafty raven.
But now, it seems their battle will go on for eternity.
I'm sick and tired of this, cried the raven.
I'm sick and tired of this, cried the prince as well.
The raven escaped from the pages of the story,
and the prince pursued the fell creature.
In the end, the prince took out his own heart
and sealed the raven away by using a forbidden power.
Just then, a murmur came from somewhere.
This is great, said the old man who was supposed to have died.
Quan
Quai
I want, I want to dance with him too, with the prince, but I'm a duck, and voice and
looks just a duck. I can't dance with him, I can't even hold his hand. And the prince's
eyes always look so lonely. Won't you laugh? Please show me your smile, my prince.
What?
Well, well, you care for him, don't you?
A little duck like you.
Wahoo! Monster!
Huh?
Whoa!
Morning has come again into our dormitory at Gold Crown Academy. The girls are waiting now. Last night, the dream I had, it was so weird and frightening.
Morning!
Oh, wait, wait! Oh, I said wait!
Oh, Jaffa, your leg's all better.
Hey, Teal!
Oh, I said wait!
Oh, come here!
Oh, Jaffa, your leg's all better. Hey, Teal, don't gobble it all yourself. Oh, come here!
Oh, come here! Come here!
Oh, come here!
Mom!
Your kids are going to be leaving the nest soon, aren't they? When they learn to fly, bring them
with you!
So, what was Senior Muto up to?
Oh, come here!
Hey, Mom!
Your kids are going to be leaving the nest soon, aren't they?
When they learn to fly, bring them with you!
So, what was Senior Muto up to?
I had another good dream!
I mean, yeah, me being a duck sucked as always, but at least I got to see Senior Muto again.
Him being the prince was almost too perfect.
Senior Muto, good morning!
It's the school bell!
This is terrible!
Oh, why didn't you wake me up?
PK!
Lily!
You meanies!
PK here.
Lily here.
Say, isn't it still six o'clock?
Scatterbrained as usual.
She's so cute!
Oh, I'm Duck.
My name is Duck.
Maybe that's why I have dreams like that.
Oh, my dear Senior Muto.
If I could dance a pas de deux with you even just once.
If I got to, I'd give my life for that.
Help!
I'm sorry for being late!
Huh?
There's no one here.
Why?
Huh?
There's no one here.
Why?
Uh…
Senior Mewto…
Wow…
Oh…
I'm sorry…
I…
Uh…
Well, uh…
Am I disturbing you?
I'm disturbing you, aren't I?
Of course I am, aren't I, aren't I?
Uh…
Please excuse me, I'm leaving right away!
If only my body weren't so jumbled up, I feel like I'm gonna trip, gonna trip!
My feet, my feet, my feet!
I tripped!
Uh…
Senior Mewto!
Wow…
What beautiful eyes…
I feel like they're drawing me in…
But…
They look so lonely…
It's like he's the prince I saw in my dreams…
Gah!
Gah…?
Gah…
KC….
KKK…
I'm sorry I'm so sorry I'm bothering you, huh?
I'm really such a scatterbrain, and I'm just so mad at things like everything, and on top of that I'm always too hasty like PK and Lilie say, I chuck like a duck so I'm weird…
Do you think I'm weird?
Shoot, even I think I'm weird.
I don't.
Huh?
You don't think I'm weird?
I don't.
I can't believe it.
No one's ever said that to me.
Hey.
Fakir.
Senor Fakir!
Did I not tell you to inform me when you go out?
Yes.
We're going.
Stand up.
What's wrong?
My foot.
Foot?
Did you twist it?
Idiot.
Huh?
What?
It was my fault.
He saved me when I tripped and-
What were you thinking doing such a pointless thing?
So like I said, he was protecting me.
That's why I said pointless.
Stand up.
We're going back.
You don't have to be so rough with him.
Quiet.
Pointless, huh?
Well, sure, maybe, but you don't have to say it quite so bluntly,
you know.
Huh?
The bell again?
What?
My butt, if you'd just taken the time to look at the clock-
I was panicked, okay?
And that's what makes you so cute.
Always be our clumsy, scatterbrained duck.
But hey, you have the great honor of talking with Fakir, so it's okay.
He isn't a very nice person.
What'd you say?
You know Fakir's the best.
Oh no, the best is Senior Muto!
Oh, duck.
The wonderful Muto has already got Rue.
A doomed love, a duck destined for heartbreak.
The teacher's here.
Yes.
Cat?
That's Mr. Cat.
Mr. Cat?
Something wrong?
A cat for a teacher?
All right, quiet down.
If you don't...
Rest assured, I will have you marry me.
Start in first position, now, relevé, and move your arms to second position, remember,
straight leg, and now third position, arms on low, that's it.
Don't stick your bottoms out.
Senior Muto, why did his eyes look so lonely?
Bottom, your mind was somewhere else, wasn't it?
If you do not focus, then I will have you marry me.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
All right.
We will now observe a performance by the Special Clash.
Members of the Special Clash, entre vous.
Wow!
Rue!
Chi-si-si-si-zu-si-si-xi-si-si-si-u-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si-si
Wow, so pretty.
Yes, unlike Doug.
Now she's depressed.
Oh, no, she really got depressed?
Oh, how cute!
For Senior Muto, it'd have to be someone like Rue to make a good match.
So sad.
I won't indulge you anymore.
This time I will have you married.
Sorry, Doug was just so moved she couldn't help but cry out.
She's taxing but cute, so please forgive her.
I still haven't made a proper apology to Senior Muto for getting him hurt.
I have to apologize.
You should be grateful to us.
You were this close to being forced to marry Mr. Cat.
Thanks.
What's wrong, Doug?
You're acting weird.
Weird.
You think it's weird to suddenly show up?
Show up?
Well, I say suddenly, but if there's no choice but suddenly, it's not weird, right?
Where's this?
Even if it is weird!
Not for you!
I just gotta go!
You gotta go where?
Okay, I'm going!
Let's go!
See, where are you going?
You're so cute!
I'm not supposed to go into the boys dormitory, but I'm just going to apologize.
So, I have to apologize.
So, and I can't apologize unless I go inside!
Oh, you stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid coward!
You're in my way!
Oh, um, is Senior Muto…
He's not here.
Yeah, so we're…
Go home!
Ouch!
How is his injury?
It's not serious.
I'd like to apologize.
There's no need.
Are you like this to everyone you talk to?
Oh, that guy really ticks me off!
Muto.
Fakir.
I told you to stay in bed.
Sorry.
Is your foot hurting?
I don't know.
What a wretch you are.
You're far too slow and utterly useless.
As for helping others, you would do best to forget such notions.
Yes.
All you need to do is listen to what I tell you.
Man.
After all that, I didn't get to make my apology.
I suck.
I wonder if his injury is okay.
Those eyes that always look so lonely.
There's gotta be some kind of reason for it, right?
Not that I can do anything about it.
But…
But if there were only some way I could help him…
If I were able to do something…
I'd give my life for that.
Huh?
What's that?
That man!
Huh?
What's that?
That man!
Huh?
What's that?
Ah!
That man!
He's not here!
Yes, I am!
Huh?
You haven't forgotten about me already, have you?
It feels strange out here.
Do you want to know? Well, do you honestly know?
Little duck?
The water has begun to flow. The time has begun to pass.
Now, tell me a story.
I'm going.
On my way back, I'll borrow some books for you from the library.
Don't read any, except for the ones I bring.
Okay, thank you.
Don't give me cause to worry, you idiot.
I just got so much to do after class. I don't know how I'm going to get it all done.
Okay, so what's okay now?
You're going to do something, right?
I wonder what?
Nothing really.
Maybe sneaking in to see Senior Mewtwo.
Oh my!
And if things go well, strike up a friendship.
Was I right?
I hadn't thought that far.
Oh no, that's the spirit you have to go with.
Somehow we'll make sure to find a way to cover you being late.
Uh, okay.
Fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight, fight.
I wonder if it'll work out.
Oh, it'll be fine.
You think?
Because even if she fails, I'll comfort her.
I have to do it for real this time.
Oh!
Canary Mom's kids leave the nest today.
Ah!
Huh?
Be careful!
Ah!
Oh no!
Oh dear, the prince is going to die.
The prince?
The hero meets his death.
Death!
What's going to happen in this story?
Please, you have to tell me what happens next.
Is the young prince going to make it?
Who in the world is going to save him?
Who?
Yes.
I wonder who?
Do you care for him, little duck?
What?
Do you want to be of help to the poor young prince?
Are you saying that you're going to tell me this story?
What?
Very well.
That's right.
I will save the prince.
I will save him.
Now, do you remember who you are?
Yes, I do.
I am Princess Tootoo.
Princess Tootoo!
Oh, oh, my God.
I'm doing it.
I am…
I'll…
Do you care for him, little duck?
What?
Do you want to be of help to the poor young prince?
Are you saying that you're going to tell me this story?
What?
Very well.
That's right.
I will save the prince.
I…
Will save him…
Now, do you remember who you are?
Yes, I do.
I am Princess Tootoo.
Flour waltz!
To be continued...
And to think I was able to save you, Mewtwo.
It's like a dream.
How do you know my name?
And you, who are you?
I am.
Who, indeed?
I am a...
You remember now, little duck?
Yes, you are a duck.
Just a bird called a duck.
Quack!
I...
So I was a duck.
Well, well.
Princess Choo-choo has gone back to being a duck.
The story has just begun.
I am a duck.
Well, well.
Princess Choo-choo has gone back to being a duck.
The story has just begun.
What to do now?
He-he-he-he-he-he-he-he-he.
I'm just a duck, and I thought I was a girl.
Oh my, if it isn't Miss Rue.
Mewtwo is going to accompany me now.
Anteater?
Would you dance with me?
Rue, you know, I'm really terrible at this,
so I don't think I'm going to be any good to you at all.
Don't worry, just follow my directions.
I'm the feeling of bitter disappointment,
shattered and forgotten.
I really and truly have been able to become Princess Tutu.
All you children who love stories, come gather round.
Thank you.